indiater.com 2018-05-11

# Privacy Policy - Indiater

**What information do we collect?**  
We collect information from you when you register on [www.indiater.com](http://indiater.com/), place an order, subscribe to our newsletter.  
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:  
• To improve our website  
• To improve customer service  
• To process transactions  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.  
• To send periodic emails

**Third party links**  
Sometimes, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites.

**Your Consent**  
By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, send an email notifying you of any changes, and update the Privacy Policy modification date below.
